University Relations, Office of; Records ua760
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Press Releases, 1961-1995; 4.5 cubic ft.
  - Press Releases, 1985 August (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Press Releases, 1985 September (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Press Releases, 1985 October (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Press Releases, 1985 November (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Press Releases, 1985 December (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Degree Recipients, 1985 December (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Press Releases, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Press Releases, 1986 January (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Press Releases, 1986 February (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Press Releases, 1986 March (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Press Releases, 1986 April (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Press Releases, 1986 May (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Degree Recipients, 1986 May (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Press Releases, 1986 June (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Press Releases, 1986 July (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Press Releases, 1986 August (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Press Releases, 1986 September (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Press Releases, 1986 October (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Press Releases, 1986 November (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Press Releases, 1986 December (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Press Releases, 1987 January (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Press Releases, 1987 February (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Press Releases, 1987 March (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Press Releases, 1987 April (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Press Releases, 1987 May (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Press Releases, 1987 June (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Press Releases, 1987 July (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Press Releases, 1987 August (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Press Releases, 1987 September (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Press Releases, 1987 October (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Press Releases, 1987 November (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Press Releases, 1988 January (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Press Releases, 1988 February (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Press Releases, 1988 March (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Press Releases, 1988 April (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Press Releases, 1988 May (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Press Releases, 1988 June (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Press Releases, 1988 July (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Press Releases, 1988 August (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Press Releases, 1988 September (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Press Releases, 1988 October (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Press Releases, 1988 November (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Press Releases, 1988 December (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Press Releases, 1989 January (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Press Releases, 1989 February (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Press Releases, 1989 March (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Press Releases, 1989 April (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Press Releases, 1989 May (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Press Releases, 1989 June (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Press Releases, 1989 July (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Press Releases, 1989 August (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Press Releases, 1989 September (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Press Releases, 1989 October (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Press Releases, 1989 November (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Press Releases, 1989 December (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Press Releases, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Press Releases, 1990 January (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Press Releases, 1990 February (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Press Releases, 1990 March (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Press Releases, 1990 April (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Press Releases, 1990 May (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Press Releases, 1990 June (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Press Releases, 1990 July (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Press Releases, 1990 August (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Press Releases, 1990 September (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Press Releases, 1990 October (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Press Releases, 1990 November (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Press Releases, 1990 December (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Press Releases, 1991 January (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Press Releases, 1991 February (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1991 March (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1991 April (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1991 May (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1991 June (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1991 July (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1991 August (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1991 September (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1991 October (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1991 November (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1991 December (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases Duplicates, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1992 January (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases, 1992 February (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases, 1992 March (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1992 April (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1992 May (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1992 June (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1992 August (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1992 September (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 1992 October (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases, 1992 November (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1992 December (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Press Releases Duplicates, 1992 January 5 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Press Releases Duplicates, 1992 June 12 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Press Releases, 1993 January (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1993 February (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1993 March (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1993 April (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1993 June (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1993 July (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1993 August (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1993 September (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1993 October (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1993 November (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 1993 December (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases Duplicates, 1993 January 5 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases Duplicates, 1993 June 12 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1994 January (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1994 February (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1994 March (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1994 April (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1994 May (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1994 June (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1994 July (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1994 August (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1994 September (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1994 October (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 1994 November (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1994 December (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases Duplicates, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases, 1995 January (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1995 February (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1995 March (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1995 April (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1995 May (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1995 June (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1995 July (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 1995 August (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases, 1995 September (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1995 October (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Press Releases, 1995 November (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Press Releases, 1995 December (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Publications, 1960-1999; 9 cubic ft.
  Files have been maintained in their original order upon processing and are largely arranged alphabetically.
  This series appears to have served as a reference file of university-related publications maintained by the Office. These include publications created by interest groups affiliated with the school (such as New York Environmental News) and promotional materials created by the school itself (such as admissions mailers).
  Additionally, the collection includes a chronological collection of the University Update, which was published at the time by the University Relations Office.
- Athletics, 1967-1991; 7 cubic ft.
  This series is made up of files maintained by the Office on the university's athletic programs. Files in this series document competitions and coaching hires of the university's varsity as well as junior varsity athletic teams, with a focus on men's basketball and football. This series contains press releases and press clippings, team statistics and schedules, and publications including game-day programs and press guides. It also contains correspondence from the period in which the school transitioned to Division I athletics.
  Files in this series have largely been order based upon original writing and labels on storage boxes.
  - Sports Release, 1966 September 29; 1967 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sports Release, 1967 April 4; 1968 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sports Release, 1968 April 4; 1968 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sports Release, 1969 January 2; 1969 September 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sports Release, 1969 September 16; 1970 February 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Sports Release, 1970 February 20; 1970 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sports Release, 1970 January 4; 1971 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sports Release, 1972 November 6; 1973 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sports Release, 1972 March 24; 1972 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sports Release, 1971 November 16; 1972 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sports Release, 1973 July 2; 1973 November 28 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Sports Release, 1973 December 5; 1974 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sports Release, 1974 September 12; 1975 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sports Release, 1975 March 3; 1975 December 22 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Sports Release, 1996 January 7; 1976 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sports Release, 1976 October 4; 1977 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sports Release, 1977 February 4; 1977 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sports Release, 1977 August 22; 1977 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sports Release, 1977 November 2; 1978 March (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Sports Release, 1979 March; 1979 October (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Sports Release, 1978 November; 1979 March (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Sports Release, 1978 April; 1978 October (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Sports Release, 1979 November; 1980 June (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sports, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sports statistics, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Sports statistics, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sports statistics, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sports statistics, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sports statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sports statistics, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sports statistics, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Sports statistics, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sports Programs (Old), 1981; 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Sports Cross Country, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sports Hoop game Summaries, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sports Hoop game Statistics, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sports Hoop Statistics, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sports NCAA Host, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Baseball, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sports baseball, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sports Men's basketball, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Sports basketball, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Sports Men's basketball, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sports basketball, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Sports NCAA Tourneys, 1968-1969; 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Sports Men's Tennis, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Sports Football, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Sports Releases Weekly Reports, 1984 January; 1985 May (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Sports basketball statistics, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Sports Men's Soccer, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Sports Football Prospects, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Sports Football, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Sports Men's Cross Country, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Sports Men's Soccer, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Sports Wrestling, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Sports Men's Track and field, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Men's indoor track, 1985; 1986 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Sports Men's Track and field, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Men's Track, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Sports Wrestling, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Sports Men's/Women's basketball, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Sports Cross Country Women's, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Sports Lacrosse, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Sports Women's NCAA Basketball, 1986 March (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Sports Women's Basketball, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Sports Women's Cross Country, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Women's Cross Country, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Sports Women's Soccer, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Women's Soccer, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Sports Woman's Softball, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Sports Woman's Swimming, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Sports Woman's Tennis, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Sports Woman's Softball, 1985 Fall/Spring (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Sports Woman's Tennis, 1986 Fall (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Sports Women's indoor track, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Sports Woman's Track and field, 1985 Spring (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Sports Women's Track and field, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Sports Volleyball, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Sports Sunyac Champ Releases, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Sports Women's Volleyball, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Sports Gymnastics, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Swimming Men's/Women, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Sports Gymnastics, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Sports Tennis NCAA Nat L Tournament, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Sports Hall of Fame, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Soccer (Men's), 1967-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sports, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sports Guides, 1969-1971; 1978; 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - football, 1974-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Baseball (Men's), 1973-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Lacrosse, 1968-1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Woman's Softball, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Basketball (Women's), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Crews and lacrosse (men's), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Basketball (Women's), 1984; 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Basketball (men's), 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Football, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Basketball (men's), 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Basketball (men's), 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Soccer (women's), 1982; 1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Men's Tennis, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - NCAA Men's Wrestling, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Woman's Tennis, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Graduate Lists, 1985 Spring (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Sports Football History, 1970-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Softball (women's), 1972; 1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Volleyball (women's), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Basketball (men's), 1967-1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Football, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Cross Country Track Field (men's), 1966-1986; 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Football Grades, 1974-1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Golf and Tennis program guides, 1968-1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Gymnastics Women, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Synchronized Swimming (women's), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Wrestling (men's), 1968-1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Summer Sports camps, 1980-1982; 1984 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Sports Programs and Releases, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Basketball Clipping, 1969 December 18; 1970 December 30 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Basketball Clipping, 1970 January 1; 1971 December 31 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Basketball Clipping, 1971 January 7; 1972 April 14 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Basketball Clipping, 1972 September 26; 1973 February 25 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Basketball Clipping, 1973 March 1; 1974 April 5 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Basketball Clipping, 1974 September 27; 1976 January 28 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Basketball Clipping, 1976 February 1; 1977 January 16 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Basketball Clipping, 1977 January 19; 1977 April 12 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Basketball Clipping, 1977 November 17; 1978 February 28 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Basketball Clipping, 1978 March 2; 1978 March 17 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sports Clippings (Men's Basketball), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sports Clipping Men's Football, basketball, wrestling women's track, 1987; 1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Sports Clippings, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Sports Clippings, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Sports Baseball, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Baseball Box Sheets, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Sports Release I, 1978 March 1; 1983 October 31 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Sport Releases, 1978; 1978 January; 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Sport Releases 1-109, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Sport Releases 180-350, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Sport Releases, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Sport Releases, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Sport Releases, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Sport Releases weekly reports, 1981 November; 1983 December (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Football (Sports Release), 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Sports Releases, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Basketball (men's) News Release, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Sports Release, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Sports Release, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sports Release (missing issue), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases (90/1-90/122), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sports Release (men's woman's basketball, football, baseball, wrestling woman's track/soccer), 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sports Releases (85/1-85/63), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sports Releases (87/51-87/151), 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sports Releases (88/1-88/138) men's/woman's basketball men's/women's swimming football., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Men's Soccer, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Football (miscellaneous), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Men's Cross Country, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Women's Volleyball, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Men's hoop stats, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Men's Nv Basketball, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Statistics Men's Basketball, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Women's Track and Field (Schedules, Sports Publicity Forms), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Sportswear Computer Ware, 1987 July (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - ECAC UPSTATE, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Football, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Articles Sports, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Football- opponents, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Women's Basketball, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Football Photos, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Basketball, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Football, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Sports Schedules, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Albany vs (OHLAND Football), 1987 October 17 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Albany vs (St. Lawrence Football), 1987 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Albany vs (HOFSTKA Football), 1987 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Albany vs (Brockport Football), 1987 September 26 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Albany vs (Western Conn Football), 1987 September 19 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Albany vs (Norwich Football), 1987 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Albany vs (Ithaca 15-14), 1987 September 12 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - RpI vs (Albany Football), 1987 September 24 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Lacrosse, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Women's Soccer, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Men's Soccer, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Football newspaper cups, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Winter Sports Clip, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Volleyball, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Men's Track and Field, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Women's Track and Field, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Gymnastics, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Women's X-C, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Men's X-C, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Women's Tennis, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Men's Tennis, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Softball, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Women's Track and Field, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Football Records, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Independent Status, 1986 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Receipts, Undated; 1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Football and Basketball Brochures, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Football Photos, Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Wrestling, 1988 January 15; 1988 January 16 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cross-Country Women, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Men's Tennis, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Women's Soccer, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Hall of Fame, 1984 June (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Wrestling (1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Wrestling (2 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Men's Cross Country, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Crew (men's/women), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Women's Tennis, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Volleyball Coach: Patrick Dwyer, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Football Banquet + Awards, 1985 December 8 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Men's Soccer, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Softball, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Women's Basketball Statistics, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Event Flyers, Clippings, Parent Letter, 1986 February 25; 1986 March 1; 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Stats All TIME Records, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Baseball, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Basketball Statistics, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Men's Swimming, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Women's Basketball Coach Mari Warner, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Men's Basketball Coach Dr. Richard Sausers, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Lacrosse, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - News (Office of Media Relations Press Releases), 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Sportsfest, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Sportscast, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Sportscast, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Sports Bulletin, 1966 November 8; 1968 February 28 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Sportscast, 1968 March 5; 1971 December 15 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Press Clippings, 1965 November; 1966 February (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Press Clippings, 1966 February 26; 1967 September 2 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Published News Record, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Published News Record, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Published News Record, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Published News Record, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Photographs, 1967-1995; undated; 4.5 cubic feet
  This series is made up of photographs and negative sheets. The photographs and negative sheets in this series document various University events and appear to have been taken either for or by employees of the office. The collection includes a mix of posed and candid photographs of students and faculty as well as photographs of major events including graduation ceremonies.
  At one time the office appears to have been responsible for the creation of the Carillon and UAlbany Magazine; as such, some of the files in this series contain photographs and graphics prepared for the magazine.
  Files in this series have been maintained in their original order upon transfer. Most photographic files were arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Negatives and Diapositives, 1969; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified, 1972; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni, 1979 April; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Apollo Agonistes Conference, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arnold, Norman, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Art Department, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Art Gallery, 1976 July 12; 1978 July (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Atmospheric Sciences, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Becker, Ben, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Biology, 1974 July (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Business, School of, 1975 September (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Byng, Dennis, 1978 July (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Campus Center, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Campus- Downtown, 1980 November 5 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Campus Uptown, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Center For Women in Government, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chemistry, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Classrooms, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Computer Center, 1978 July (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Counseling, 1979 January (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dance, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dorm Life, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Downtime Albany, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Education, 1974 July (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Empire State Plaza, 1979 June (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Faculty, A-F, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Faculty, F-M, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Faculty, M-S, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Faculty, W, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)